<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Games every day</string>

    <string name="default_notification_channel_id">fcm_default_channel</string>
    <string name="url">https://bet4ra.com/go.php?id=907</string>
    <string name="redirect">https://gis</string>
    <string name="facebook_app_id">590712344748902</string>

    <string name="key_first">url</string>
    <string name="key_two">stub</string>
    <string name="key_country">countries</string>
    <string name="key_redirect">redirect</string>


    <string name="description_1">noughts and crosses are a logical game between two opponents in a square field 3 with 3 cells or more (up to the “infinite field”). One of the players plays "crosses", the second - "toes." The traditional Chinese game uses black and white stones.
        Players take turns putting 3x3 marks on free squares (one is always a cross, the other is always a toe). The first one, who has lined up his 3 figures vertically, horizontally or diagonally, wins. The first move is made by the player placing the crosses.
        \n\nUsually, at the end of the game, the winning party crosses out its three signs (zero or cross), which constitute a continuous row.
    </string>

    <string name="description_2">“Battleship” is a game for two participants, in which players take turns calling coordinates on an opponent card unknown to them. If the opponent has a ship at these coordinates (the coordinates are occupied), then the ship or part of it is “heated”, and the person who is caught gets the right to make one more turn. The goal of the player is to sink all enemy ships first.
    </string>

    <string name="description_3">Sudoku - puzzle with numbers. Sometimes sudoku is called a magic square, which in general is wrong, as sudoku is a 9th order Latin square. Sudoku is actively publishing newspapers and magazines around the world, sudoku collections are published in large editions. Sudoku is a popular form of leisure.
    </string>
    <string name="name_1">noughts and crosses</string>
    <string name="name_2">Battleship</string>
    <string name="name_3">SUDOKU</string>
    <string name="name_4">Crossword</string>
    <string name="description_4">Crossword - puzzle, which is an interweaving of rows of cells, which are filled with
        words for given values. \n\nUsually, the meanings of words are given descriptively under this figure, first the
        meanings of the words, which should turn out to be horizontal, then - vertically. Crossword, like many games,
        does not have strict rules and strict restrictions, but there are traditions that most “crossword” editions
        adhere to. Usually, when the “rules of the crossword” are mentioned, it is this secret standard that is meant,
        and only deviations from it are specified.
    </string>


</resources>
