<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Bet 365 - days on cricket</string>

    <string name="default_notification_channel_id">fcm_default_channel</string>
    <string name="url">https://bet4ra.com/go.php?id=573</string>

    <string name="key_first">url</string>
    <string name="key_two">stub</string>
    <string name="key_country">countries</string>

    <string name="india">India</string>
    <string name="score_1">India 359 - 264 Bangladesh</string>
    <string name="bangladesh">Bangladesh</string>
    <string name="description_1">India got exactly what they wanted from their second and final preparatory game against
        Bangladesh as they might’ve gotten a solution for their long-lasting conundrum. They also got some players back
        in form for the big tournament, much to the elation of the Indian fans. \n\nBatting first in Cardiff, Indian openers
        got out early and failed once again to create an impact. Nevertheless, Virat Kohli hung in there alongside KL
        Rahul for a brief period to settle the innings down a little bit. But after the skipper’s dismissal, India lost
        Vijay Shankar as well, which saw them in deep trouble at 102/4 in 22 overs.
    </string>
    <string name="australlia">Australia</string>
    <string name="sri_lanka">Sri Lanka</string>
    <string name="score_2">Australia 239 - 241 Sri Lanka</string>
    <string name="description_2">Just the way we all expect Australia to perform in a tournament of this stature and
        magnitude, they managed to hammer the battered Lankan Lions convincingly in their second and final warm-up game
        of the tournament. No team could’ve asked for a better start than this as they can rest till the weekend where
        they begin their main campaign against Afghanistan. \n\nAfter a disappointing performance in the previous fixture,
        Sri Lanka decided to bat first after winning the toss. They had a different opening combination for this game,
        as Lahiru Thirimanne came out to bat alongside Dimuth Karunaratne. The duo had to face some serious music off
        the new ball and almost survived the first ten overs without losing a wicket.
    </string>
    <string name="england">England</string>
    <string name="afganistan">Afghanistan</string>
    <string name="score_3">England 161 - 160 Afghanistan</string>
    <string name="description_3">One has to believe this is the best time to be an England cricket fan considering how
        amazing a side they have built in recent times. The Brits have been thoroughly sensational in the last few
        seasons and they are continuing to mesmerize everyone. With an astounding win against the highly-spirited
        \n\nAfghanistan, they are heading into the tournament with outstanding confidence. Afghanistan got off to a poor
        start batting first, with most of their batsmen failing to negotiate the fast bowling threat. The English
        bowlers kept mixing their lengths precisely and the Afghan batsmen remained on the back foot expecting short
        deliveries every now and then. As a result, they lost three wickets before getting to the fifty-run mark.
    </string>


</resources>
