<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Bet 365 - days on cricket</string>

    <string name="default_notification_channel_id">fcm_default_channel</string>
    <string name="url">https://bet4ra.com/go.php?id=573</string>

    <string name="key_first">url</string>
    <string name="key_two">stub</string>
    <string name="key_country">countries</string>
    <string name="news_1">MI rope in Beuran Hendricks as Joseph\'s replacement</string>
    <string name="news_1_desc">Mumbai Indians have signed up left-arm pacer Beuran Hendricks as replacement for the
        injured Alzarri Joseph for the rest of the Indian Premier League 2019. The South African pacer has previously
        been a part of King XI Punjab\'s set-up in IPL. Joseph sustained an injury on his right arm during MI\'s game
        against Rajasthan Royals at the Wankhede stadium on April 13. The West Indian pacer, who came in as a
        replacement for the injured Adam Milne, hurt his right arm while trying to stop a boundary hit by Shreyas Gopal
        in the 19th over of RR\'s innings. The tall fast bowler had earlier taken his career best T20 figures of 6 for
        12 against Sunrisers Hyderabad. Hendricks, the 28-year-old, has played 64 T20s, picking up 89 scalps at an
        average of just over 20. He has also played two ODIs and 10 T20Is for South Africa MI lock horns against Chennai
        Super Kings in their next IPL 2019 game in Chennai on April 26.
    </string>
    <string name="news_2">Pant, Dhawan propel Delhi Capitals to the top</string>
    <string name="news_2_desc">The left-hander put on show all the shots that have made him such an important prospect.
        He pulled and hooked with glee, even if he got himself into some strange positions while doing so. The slog
        sweep over fine leg was there too, as was the finely timed drive, and lofted flicks. Coming in after the fall of
        Dhawan and Shreyas Iyer\'s wickets, Pant needed to ensure he plugged the opening while also making sure his side
        did not fall too far behind the asking rate. His game plan was near perfect. He massively preferred the leg
        side, scoring almost 80% of the runs there, but it was his maturity that stood out. He scored 6 fours and 2
        sixes in his innings, but on many occasions was adept at picking the gaps and running hard for singles and
        doubles. There has been a lot of criticism thrown Rishabh Pant\'s way after he has thrown his wicket away with
        Delhi in winning positions. He saw Prithvi Shaw and Sherfane Rutherford fall the same way, but he ensured he was
        there till the very end. He was unbeaten on 78 off 36 by the end, and would have delighted the team by showing
        that he can indeed finish off games.
    </string>
    <string name="news_3">The curious case of CSK\'s batting woes</string>
    <string name="news_3_desc">Shane Watson, Faf du Plessis, Suresh Raina, Ambati Rayudu, Kedar Jadhav, MS Dhoni,
        Ravindra Jadeja and Dwayne Bravo. You\'ll be hard pushed to find a rival for this batting line-up in the IPL.
        Royal Challengers Bangalore may have the best two in the business, the Delhi Capitals may own the cream of
        India\'s youth and the Knight Riders may have Andre Russell, but in cricket as in politics - 2 + 2 is not always
        equal to 4. Yet, for all the pedigree in the line-up, CSK have had a dire season with the bat so far, with only
        MS Dhoni aggregating more than 250 (314 at 104.67) so far. \"We\'ve got a very talented batting order, which has
        been, you\'d say, consistent throughout the years. You look at the side on paper and you\'d say it\'s a
        strength, but unfortunately, we just haven\'t been able to string together partnerships or individual scores
        this year,\" head coach Stephen Fleming remarked after the close loss to the RCB. What\'s ailing this once
        powerful batting failure?
    </string>


</resources>
